(Howard:)I told you. Turn them inside out.
(Bernadette:)And I told you to bite me.
(Leonard:)Trying to have a magical night here, guys.
- Oh, son of a bitch.
- What?
- Nothing. Nothing.
- No, tell me.
(Penny:)It's just this guy I used to date.
(Penny:)Oh.
(Penny:)Until he cheated on me with my friend
Gretchen, who's here with him.
- You're kidding.
- And it looks like she lost a lot of weight.
(Penny:)Damn it.
(Leonard:)I know it's not ideal,
but don't let them ruin our night.
(Penny:)No, you're totally right.
She could be skinny because she's dying.
(Leonard:)That's the spirit.
Screw them. Our night's gonna be
way more special than theirs.
(Bernadette:)Uh-oh.
(Leonard:)What?
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
- Oh, my God! Yes! Of course I'll marry you!
- Ha, ha.